<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Sound Volume Notifier</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="btCancel">Cancel Repeating Timer</string>
    <string name="btStart">Start Repeating Timer</string>
    <string name="display_help">Help</string>
    <string name="display_about">About</string>
    <string name="quit_application_by_force_stop">Quit application\n (by Force Stop)</string>
    <string name="help">The Sound Volume Notifier constantly informs the phone owner about the current volume level
        of ring, alarm and media. When you start the application it shows a persistent notification in the status bar.
        A notification icon is generated dynamically and displays the levels of the ring and the alarm.
        The icon also indicates when the media volume is low. If the volume is less than 4, the separator
        between the two numbers is changed from a colon to an underscore.\n
        Once started the application is registered for automatic launch after restarting the phone. \n
        The application uses a repeating timer and checks volumes every minute, updating the notification accordingly.\n
        To pause the Notifier you need to CANCEL REPEATING TIMER. To resume you need to START REPEATING TIMER.\n
        If the Notifier is paused, it will start again after the phone restart.
        To completely disable the application you can tap QUIT APPLICATION and tap
        Force stop in the Application Info screen.\n
        \n
        Tips.\n
        - The application checks volumes immediately after its opening.
        Thus, you don’t have to wait a minute to see the current volumes. Just open the Notifier.\n
        - You can change the ring volume directly in this application.
    </string>
    <string name="about">\n
        Version 1.0 (2019)\n\n
        Author: Yury Dubinsky \n\n
        Email: small.mobile.tools@gmail.com \n\n
        This viewer is free and open source. \n\n https://github.com/dyura/SoundVolumeNotify \n\n\n
        _______________________________________________________________________
    </string>
</resources>
